cloudsurfing.com 2013-03-13

# Privacy Policy - CloudSurfing

| 

|  |  |  |  |   
---  
Privacy Policy  
  
|  |  CloudSurfing LLC recognizes that privacy is important and respects each individuals right to personal privacy. We will use the information collected through our Web site only in the ways disclosed in this statement. This statement applies to information collected at cloudsurfing.com and not 3rd party sites that we review--if you choose to visit these sites. When you click on links to other Web sites, we encourage you to read their privacy policies. Their standards may differ from ours.   
---|---  
  
    Please review this document to see:  
|    

  1. What information we collect and how we use it.
  2. How you can access and change your Account information.
  3. What security procedures are in place to protect the information.
  4. How to contact us if there are any problems or concerns.

  |    
  
    What information do we collect and how do we use it?   
  |    
We try to collect only what is reasonably necessary to help you get the most out of the CloudSurfing services and to connect with the community. If we use your information in a way different than for the purposes of CloudSurfing, then we will ask you for your permission prior to doing so. 

  * **Registered Users:** If you create an account to take advantage of all that ClouodSurfing has to offer, then we record information that you include in your account settings page. We will use your your email to communicate with you. Others will be able to view your publicly available information to better connect with you. Registered users may receive additional announcements from us about our services from time to time, but out of respect for the privacy of our users, we present the option to not receive any of these communications. 
  * **Submitted Content:** We may publicly display your submitted reviews, suggestions, lists, videos, screenshots, ratings, and comments in order to provide our services. When we show your submitted content, we recognize your contribution with your community name. Please be advised that submitted content becomes public knowledge.
  * **Review Information:** Website review information is supplied to help CloudSurfing users effectively review the offering. Much of the information posted about the listed sites has been contributed by our community and researchers.
  * **Questions and Feedback:** If you contact us with feedback and questions, we will record whatever information you provide to communicate with you. 
  * **Activity on the Site:** We record information from your use of the Site, such as pages viewed, type of browser, IP address, URLs, and timestamps. We use this information to evaluate website statistics as a whole and learn how to better serve public users and registered community users. We also display your site activity on our community page and on your profile page so that others can be aware of your review activity. This also helps us avoid gaming and poor quality contributions by having multiple eyes on community activity. We also use your submitted activity to contribute to the collective intelligence and offer aggregated data insights. These insights will not include personally identifiable information.
  * **Cookies and Session Variables:** Like many websites, we CloudSurfing makes use of cookies and session variables. A cookie is a small text file that our Web server places on a user's computer hard drive. Cookies enable CloudSurfing LLC to deliver customized content to users. Our persistent cookies may not have an expiration date but can be easily removed by following the instructions in your browser documentation. 

  |    
  
    How you can access and change your information  
  | 

Users may access and control their own personal information by logging into their MyWeb account and changing what others can see. Users may delete their personal information from our database by emailing us at privacy@cloudsurfing.com and requesting us to remove their information.  

  |    
  
    What security procedures are in place to protect your information  
  | 

To help secure your information, access to your CloudSurfing data is password-protected. Moreover, we do not see your passwords for our third party authentication methods as you are physically taken to the 3rd party website to authenticate.  

  |    
  
    How to contact us if there are any problems or concerns  
  | 

If problems arise, users may contact CloudSurfing LLC by email and we will follow up via a phone call for any major concerns. We are committed to resolving disputes within 48 hours if the request is reasonable.  

  |    
  | 

Email: [privacy@cloudsurfing.com](mailto:privacy@cloudsurfing.com)

If you continue to use cloudsurfing.com after changes made to our privacy policy have been sent to you or published on our site, you hereby provide your consent to the changed practices. 

**Last Updated: November 11, 2008**
